http://www.hastam.co.uk/privacy-policy-cookies/

Privacy Policy and Cookies Your data, our promise
The domain name “hastam.co.uk” is registered to Health and Safety Technology and Management Ltd, trading as Hastam. Information we collect from users of the site may be used in the following ways:
Privacy Policy
You can read our full  Privacy notice and FAQs here. We will always treat your data with the upmost respect and care. If you have any questions or concerns please contact us.
Contact Details
If you complete one of the forms on the site, we will use your details only to provide any services requested by you, or to notify you of important changes to our products and services. We do not pass any of this information on to third parties unless you specifically ask us to. If you are on our mailing list and do not wish to be, please contact us and ask to be taken off.
Site Monitoring
In addition to Google Analytics mentioned above, our hosting servers log all accesses to the site, which may include IP addresses. This information is used only for statistical purposes.
Access to Data
You have the right to be told what personal information we hold about you on our databases. Please contact us in writing if you wish to know what information we do hold or if you wish us to remove your details from our database.
Cookies
This website uses Google Analytics to monitor website traffic. This will place cookies in the cookies folder of your computer, unless you disable all cookies. These cookies are used to monitor pages visited and for how long and do not pass any personal information to us. This data tells us which pages are popular, how users find these pages, and how long they stay on the site. This information is essential to us for determining how and where to improve the site and make it easier for users to find information. If you do not want this data to be collected, you can visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout to stop Google collecting data about your visit to this or any other website.
We also use cookies to hold data entered into forms so that this is not lost when moving between pages on the website. These are ‘session cookies’ and are automatically deleted when you close the web browser. We do not use any third-party cookies to provide in-page advertising or to track your visits across different websites. Here is a useful website about cookies and the law: http://www.allaboutcookies.org and a page explaining how to disable cookies in different browsers http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/. Disabling cookies will not affect your browsing of our website but will make it harder for us to judge the efficacy of the site.
Key ServicesHealth and Safety Expert Witness
Training and Mentoring
Health and Safety Consultancy and Auditing
Safety Culture Change
Evaluation Software
Legal Register Services
Research and Development
Case Studies
Connect via Email Keep up to date with the latest from Hastam via email
Your Name
Your Email
I have read the privacy policy and agree to be contacted by email about Hastam's blogs, services, and offers.
Contact Hastam today on +44 1509 410380 or online
CONTACT HASTAM
Recent Blogs
Whose side is the expert witness on? November 30, 2020 Lost Time Stress Accidents November 23, 2020
ServicesHealth and Safety Expert Witness
Training and Mentoring
Health and Safety Consultancy and Auditing
Safety Culture Change
Evaluation Software
Legal Register Services
Research and Development
Company Address 35-37 High Street
Barrow upon Soar
Loughborough, LE12 8PY
United Kingdom
Privacy Policy and Cookies
Contact Page
@hastamsafety
© 2020 Hastam.
Registered in England No 1765152 | VAT Registration No GB 393 1015 71
Home
About
Our values and policies
People
Professor Richard Booth
Doctor Tony Boyle
Doctor Mark Cooper
Steve Fletcher
Andy Gordon
Paul Haxell
Steve Highley
Paul Mahoney
Liz Shuttleworth (MD)
Doctor Louise Smail
Nick Staley
Doctor Luise Vassie
Alan Watt
Doctor David Wenham
Bob Burnup
Downloads
Services
Contact Hastam on +44 1509 410380
Please enter your name and email address to download this PDF. All other downloads will be available without the need to fill out this form each time. Your details will not be passed to third parties.
Full Name (required)
Email Address (required)
Telephone
Please add me to your mailing list
I have read the privacy policy and agree to be contacted by email or telephone regarding the publications I have downloaded. If I have requested to be added to the mailing list then I also consent to be contacted by email about Hastam's blogs, services, and offers.
×
Be the first to hear from our experts: OPEN
Your Name
Your Email
I have read the privacy policy and agree to be contacted by email about Hastam's blogs, services, and offers.
We are using cookies to give you the best experience on our website.
You can find out more about which cookies we are using or switch them off in settings.
Accept
Change cookie settings
Privacy Overview
Strictly Necessary Cookies
3rd Party Cookies
Additional Cookies
Cookie Policy
Powered by GDPR plugin
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience possible. Cookie information is stored in your browser and performs functions such as recognising you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful.
You can adjust all of your cookie settings by navigating the tabs on the left hand side.
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Strictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.
disable
If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again.
3rd Party Cookies
This website uses Google Analytics to collect anonymous information such as the number of visitors to the site, and the most popular pages.
Keeping this cookie enabled helps us to improve our website.
disable
Please enable Strictly Necessary Cookies first so that we can save your preferences!
Additional Cookies
This website uses the following additional cookies:
Logging of publications downloaded from our downloads page
In order to download our publications from the downloads page we require you to provide your name and email address, we set a cookie to remember that you completed and sent this information so that if you return within 1 year you will not need to enter this information again provided you have not cleared your cookies since
To enable social sharing and blog entry like button
disable
Please enable Strictly Necessary Cookies first so that we can save your preferences!
Cookie Policy
More information about our Cookie Policy
Enable All
Save Changes
